# Wassim Khemici

wkhemici@berkeley.edu | 650.245.0171 | LinkedIn | Portfolio

### PROFESSIONAL SUMMARY

Content specialist with extensive writing, editing, content management, design, and marketing experience. Experienced executive-level/C-Suite and PR communications writer. Creative with a strong technical software background. Adept at quickly learning new technologies and distilling complex technical concepts into legible language. 7 years of content writing experience and 3 years of experience working with executives to create public-facing marketing content.

#### **EDUCATION**

**University of California**, Berkeley **Bachelor of Arts**, English (August 2016)

**University of California**, Berkeley Extension **Coding Full-Stack Certificate** (May 2019)

#### **TECHNICAL SKILLS**

Web Development: HTML, CSS, Cloud, JavaScript, Github, MySQL, Materialize, Bootstrap, WordPress Design/Software: Adobe Creative Suite, MS, SEO (Search Engine Optimization), and MailChimp

#### WORK EXPERIENCE

## **Content & Marketing Coordinator**

JODI Group, Inc. | San Francisco, CA

March 2017–February 2019

- Effectively wrote, edited, and managed all of the company's written copy
- Drafted internal and public-facing communications for executives, PR, and customers
- Crafted email marketing campaigns with MailChimp & direct mail campaigns to field groups
- Significantly increased views-per-article and SEO for company blog 49miles.com
- Conceptualized and managed content calendar for blog, social media accounts, and print
- Tastefully designed layouts with Adobe InDesign, Acrobat, & Lightroom
- Played an integral role in the development of the new company websites and blog

#### Freelance Writer, Tutor, and Editor

Freelance | Bay Area, CA

August 2014–Present

- Write content for Facebook Community Events to advertise to the Silicon Valley audience
- Write advertising content for the San Mateo Daily Journal to market the County Pride Center
- Edit case studies, user-experience guides, and technical documentation for programmers
- Coach undergraduates to refine their academic writing, editing, and analytic skills
- Consult with students on the creation of successful, powerful college applications

## Student Intern

Carnegie Foundation for the Advancement of Teaching | Stanford, CA

June 2013-August 2014

- Managed the company's organizational and administrative duties
- Coordinated educational seminars and research programs
- Gathered research data and created analytical reports